[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of Cassims right hand man in the Disney film Aladdin and the King of Thieves?", "correct_answer": "Saluk", "incorrect_answers": ["Bob", "Agrabah", "Midas"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In which country was eyeball jewelry, or extraocular implantation, developed in 2002?", "correct_answer": "The Netherlands", "incorrect_answers": ["The United Kingdom", "The U.S.A.", "India"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A flight attendant lands at OHare Airport in Chicago, in the winter months, and drives to Gary, Indiana. Will he or she have to reset his/ her watch upon arrival in Gary?", "correct_answer": "No", "incorrect_answers": ["Yes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This is a betting game in which two cards are initially dealt. The player may ask for an additional card, hoping to reach the ideal score of nine.", "correct_answer": "Chemin de Fer", "incorrect_answers": ["Faro", "Black Jack", "Casino"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What kind of competition does Dakota Fannings character win in the 2004 action movie Man on Fire?", "correct_answer": "A swimming race", "incorrect_answers": ["A violin contest", "A piano contest", "A horse race"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the occupation of Jim Carreys character in the 1997 movie Liar Liar?", "correct_answer": "Lawyer", "incorrect_answers": ["Pet detective", "Politician", "Police officer"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the ideal body weight for a six-foot-tall man with average bone structure?", "correct_answer": "178 pounds", "incorrect_answers": ["220 pounds", "200 pounds", "195 pounds"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which is the correct definition for oxter?", "correct_answer": "the armpit", "incorrect_answers": ["having much snow", "walrus ivory", "to polish"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What directive ordered the Clone Troopers to destroy all of the Jedi in Star Wars?", "correct_answer": "Order 66", "incorrect_answers": ["Operation 501", "Operation 66", "Order 501"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who wrote the book on which the 2008 western Appaloosa is based?", "correct_answer": "Robert B. Parker", "incorrect_answers": ["Larry McMurtry", "Edward Buscombe", "John Wayne"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What role does the carburetor have in the engine?", "correct_answer": "Mixing air and fuel", "incorrect_answers": ["Cooling", "Igniting the fuel mixture", "Cleaning"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie classic, The African Queen, what was Charlies drink of choice, until Rose forced him into sobriety?", "correct_answer": "Gin and river water", "incorrect_answers": ["Scotch and boiler water", "Straight bourbon", "Whiskey and river water"]}]